A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1971-1980 FA401
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1974
  - Ghana, 1974; 1974/496
    - G-U, 1974 (Reel 56, Frame 722)
    - Ghana - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1974; 1974/496.D
      - Agriculture, 1974 (Reel 56, Frame 896)
  - Nigeria, 1974; 1974/497
    - Nigerian Economic Society, 1974 (Reel 56, Frame 906)
    - A-O, 1974 (Reel 56, Frame 955)
    - T-U, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 1)
    - Nigeria - Medical Sciences, 1974; 1974/497.A
      - A-U, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 54)
    - Nigeria - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1974; 1974/497.D
      - Agriculture, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 58)
    - Nigeria - Fellowships, 1974; 1974/497.E
      - 497E, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 64)
      - A-O, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 67)
  - Sierra Leone, 1974; 1974/499
    - P-U, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 94)
  - France, 1974; 1974/500
    - A-R, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 105)
  - Vietnam, 1974; 1974/509
    - Vietnam Foundation for Education Development, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 295)
  - Ivory Coast, 1974; 1974/527
    - A-U, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 324)
  - Senegal, 1974; 1974/531
    - Cisse, Moctar A., 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 378)
  - Tunisia, 1974; 1974/539
    - Hedda, Ali, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 387)
  - Yemen, 1974/575
    - Yemen - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1974; 1974/575.D
      - Agriculture, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 391)
  - Asia, 1974/600
    - Asia and Far East Asia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1974; 1974/600.D
      - M-R, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 552)
  - People's Republic of China, 1974; 1974/601
    - Kwangtung College of Agriculture (Puiman), 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 615)
    - People's Republic of China - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1974; 1974/601.D
      - Agriculture, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 623)
  - Taiwan, 1974; 1974/605
    - A-Y, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 627)
  - Japan, 1974; 1974/609
    - A-Y, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 735)
  - Korea, 1974; 1974/613
    - C-W, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 777)
  - Thailand, 1974; 1974/617
    - D-W, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 810)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, 1974; 1974/617.E
      - 617E, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 1133)
      - Boonruang, Prem, 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 1138)
    - Thailand - Social Sciences, 1974; 1974/617.S
      - University of Thammasat (Economics), 1974 (Reel 57, Frame 1143)
      - University of Thammasat, Economics (Supplementary Material), 1974 (Reel 58, Frame 1)
  - Holland, 1974; 1974/650
    - B-W, 1974 (Reel 58, Frame 337)
  - Indonesia, 1974; 1974/652
    - Gadjah Mada University (B-S), 1974 (Reel 58, Frame 420)
    - D-S, 1974 (Reel 58, Frame 549)
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, 1974; 1974/652.E
      - 652E, 1974 (Reel 58, Frame 633)
      - K-U, 1974 (Reel 58, Frame 646)
  - Ethiopia, 1974; 1974/701
    - H-Z, 1974 (Reel 58, Frame 677)
    - Ethiopia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1974; 1974/701.D
      - Germplasm, 1974 (Reel 58, Frame 719)
    - Ethiopia - Fellowships, 1974; 1974/701.E
      - Bekele, Girma, 1974 (Reel 58, Frame 745)
  - Belgium, 1974; 1974/707
    - European Culture Foundation (Plan Europe 2000), 1974 (Reel 58, Frame 766)
  - Zaire, 1974; 1974/709
    - National University of Zaire (D-V), 1974 (Reel 58, Frame 768)
    - K-T, 1974 (Reel 58, Frame 906)
    - Zaire - Medical Sciences, 1974; 1974/709.A
      - National University of Zaire (Health Services), 1974 (Reel 58, Frame 922)
      - National University of Zaire, Health Services (Supplementary Material), 1974 (Reel 58, Frame 1154)
    - Zaire - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1974; 1974/709.D
      - Agriculture, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 1)
    - Zaire - Fellowships, 1974; 1974/709.E
      - E-S, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 5)
  - Yugoslavia, 1974; 1974/710
    - R-W, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 98)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1974; 1974/712
    - Opecensky, Milan, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 102)
  - Denmark, 1974; 1974/713
    - Borre, Ole, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 106)
    - Denmark - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1974; 1974/713.D
      - University of Copenhagen (Genetics), 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 109)
  - Germany, 1974; 1974/717
    - Von Schoen, Rolf, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 122)
    - B-Z, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 184)
  - Tanzania, 1974; 1974/723
    - H-U, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 274)
    - Tanzania - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1974; 1974/723.D
      - Agriculture, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 311)
    - Tanzania - Fellowships, 1974; 1974/723.E
      - B-M, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 325)
  - Zambia, 1974; 1974/724
    - University of Zambia (Igboeli, G.), 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 329)
  - Cameroon, 1974/735
    - Cameroon - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1974; 1974/735.D
      - Agriculture, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 334)
  - Italy, 1974; 1974/751
    - D-M, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 336)
  - Liberia, 1974; 1974/759
    - Guha, M. M., 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 385)
  - Norway, 1974; 1974/767
    - A-B, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 390)
  - Iran, 1974; 1974/771
    - E-U, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 394)
    - Iran - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1974; 1974/771.D
      - Agriculture, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 400)
    - Iran - Fellowships, 1974; 1974/771.E
      - Nader, Karim, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 404)
  - Portugal, 1974; 1974/773
    - A-O, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 409)
  - Romania, 1974; 1974/783
  - Finland, 1974; 1974/787
    - Pesonen, Pertti, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 520)
    - Apostoliu, Dimitrie, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 417)
  - Poland, 1974; 1974/789
    - P-U, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 523)
  - Spain, 1974; 1974/795
    - M-U, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 531)
  - Sweden, 1974; 1974/800
    - B-T, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 564)
  - Switzerland, 1974; 1974/803
    - Center for Education in International Management (Environmental Education), 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 593)
    - Center for Education in International Management, Environmental Education (Supplementary Material), 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 624)
    - C-Z, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 914)
  - Turkey, 1974; 1974/805
    - D-P, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 948)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, 1974; 1974/805.E
      - A-F, 1974 (Reel 59, Frame 1052)
  - United Arab Republic, 1974; 1974/812
    - A-K, 1974 (Reel 60, Frame 1)
    - United Arab Republic - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1974; 1974/812.D
      - Agriculture, 1974 (Reel 60, Frame 47)
  - Jordan, 1974; 1974/816
    - Jayyusi, Salma Khadra, 1974 (Reel 60, Frame 58)
    - Jordan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1974; 1974/816.D
      - Agriculture, 1974 (Reel 60, Frame 67)
  - Israel, 1974; 1974/825
    - B-T, 1974 (Reel 60, Frame 125)
  - Lebanon, 1974; 1974/833
    - A-H, 1974 (Reel 60, Frame 205)
    - Lebanon - Medical Sciences, 1974; 1974/833.A
      - American University of Beirut, 1974 (Reel 60, Frame 515)
    - Lebanon - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1974; 1974/833.D
      - Agriculture, 1974 (Reel 60, Frame 556)
  - Members and Meetings, 1974; 1974/903
    - Election, 1974 (Reel 60, Frame 564)
    - Notices, 1974 (Reel 60, Frame 585)
    - B-W, 1974 (Reel 60, Frame 610)
  - Humanities, 1974/911
    - Humanities - Fellowships, 1974; 1974/911.E
      - R-S, 1974 (Reel 60, Frame 725)
  - Environmental Affairs, 1974/927
    - Environmental Affairs - Fellowships, 1974; 1974/927.E
      - Oregon State University, 1974 (Reel 60, Frame 782)
- General Correspondence, 1975
  - International, 1975; 1975/100
    - Allen, Jane, 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 1)
    - Almy, Susan W., 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 3)
    - Anderson, R. Glenn, 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 6)
    - Arbab, Farzam, 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 11)
    - Baldwin, William, 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 32)
    - Barker, Randolph, 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 34)
    - Barnes, Allan C., 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 38)
    - Barnish, Guy, 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 170)
    - Bartholomew, Richard K., 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 174)
    - Berry, Elmer G., 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 187)
    - Bird, 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 189)
    - Black, Joseph E., 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 193)
    - Borlaug, Norman E., 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 197)
    - Bourne, Leo F., 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 200)
    - Bradfield, Richard, 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 204)
    - Bronte, D. Lydia, 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 206)
    - Byrnes, Francis C., 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 259)
    - Chandler, Robert F., Jr., 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 268)
    - Christie, John D., 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 332)
    - Coleman, James S., 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 338)
    - Colton, Joel, 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 348)
    - Compton, Boyd R., 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 474)
    - Connell, Elizabeth, 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 508)
    - Cook, Joseph A., 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 520)
    - Court, David, 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 572)
    - Crow, William L., 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 574)
    - Cummings, Ralph W., Jr., 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 576)
    - Dalton, Peter, 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 812)
    - Davidson, Agnes, 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 815)
    - Davis, L. Harlan, 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 819)
    - Delehanty, George E., 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 865)
    - Dinning, James S., 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 867)
    - Douglas, Johnson E., 1975 (Reel 1, Frame 963)
    - Downs, Wilbur G., 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 1)
    - Durana, Ines, 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 6)
    - Finfrock, Dwight, 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 133)
    - Freeman, Wayne H., 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 146)
    - Gilpatric, Chadbourne, 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 227)
    - Golden, William G., 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 230)
    - Gould, David J., 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 258)
    - Grant, Ulysses J., 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 283)
    - Gray, Clarence C. III, 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 460)
    - Harrar, J. George, 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 488)
    - Harwood, Richard R., 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 507)
    - Harwood, Roland E., 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 512)
    - Hayes, Guy S., 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 542)
    - Helfrich, Philip, 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 611)
    - Hildebrand, Peter E., 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 667)
    - Holland, Robert C., 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 733)
    - House, Leland R., 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 755)
    - Ingles, Thelma, 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 787)
    - Jackson, Ben R., 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 812)
    - Jennings, Peter R., 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 861)
    - Jensen, James H., 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 899)
    - Johnson, Elmer C., 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 902)
    - Johnson, Loyd, 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 908)
    - Johnston, James E., 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 954)
    - Jordan, Peter, 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 982)
    - Katz, Stephen M., 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 1020)
    - Klein, Howard, 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 1026)
    - Knowles, John H. (Africa Trip), 1975 (Reel 2, Frame 1066)
    - Knowles, John H. (China Diary), 1975 (Reel 3, Frame 1)
    - Knowles, John H. (January), 1975 (Reel 3, Frame 77)
    - Knowles, John H. (February), 1975 (Reel 3, Frame 290)
    - Knowles, John H. (March), 1975 (Reel 3, Frame 329)
    - Knowles, John H. (April), 1975 (Reel 3, Frame 373)
    - Knowles, John H. (May), 1975 (Reel 3, Frame 446)
    - Knowles, John H. (June), 1975 (Reel 3, Frame 483)
    - Knowles, John H. (July), 1975 (Reel 3, Frame 594)
    - Knowles, John H. (August), 1975 (Reel 3, Frame 718)
    - Knowles, John H. (September), 1975 (Reel 3, Frame 731)
    - Knowles, John H. (October), 1975 (Reel 3, Frame 831)
    - Knowles, John H. (November), 1975 (Reel 3, Frame 918)
    - Knowles, John H. (December), 1975 (Reel 3, Frame 1019)
    - Krishner, Leo, 1975 (Reel 3, Frame 1103)
    - Kritz, Mary M., 1975 (Reel 3, Frame 1105)
    - Kuperman, Albert S., 1975 (Reel 3, Frame 1109)
    - Laird, Reggie J., 1975 (Reel 3, Frame 1112)
    - Lathem, Willoughby, 1975 (Reel 3, Frame 1124)
    - Long, E. Croft, 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 1)
    - MacLellan, Neil B., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 21)
    - Maier, John, 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 38)
    - Maner, Jerome H., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 56)
    - Mann, Charles K., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 72)
    - McClintock, Barbara, 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 77)
    - McClung, A. Colin, 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 79)
    - McKelvey, John J., Jr., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 156)
    - Miller, 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 343)
    - Moomaw, James C., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 347)
    - Moore, Charles L., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 391)
    - Morris, O. Frank, 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 400)
    - Moseman, Albert H., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 423)
    - Neumann, Ellsworth T., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 489)
    - Nickel, John L., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 491)
    - Niederhauser, John S., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 524)
    - Northrup, Robert S., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 531)
    - Novak, Michael, 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 559)
    - Nyberg, Albert J., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 567)
    - Olson, James A., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 569)
    - Olson, William C., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 605)
    - Oshima, Harry T., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 673)
    - Osler, Robert D., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 707)
    - Owens, Patrick N., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 719)
    - Parker, Dorothy, 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 732)
    - Parson, William, 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 766)
    - Perry, Jesse P., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 792)
    - Pino, John A., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 804)
    - Plank, Stephen J., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 870)
    - Prentice, Michael A., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 893)
    - Rachie, Kenneth O., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 896)
    - Raun, Ned S., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 904)
    - Renfro, Bobby L., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 912)
    - Richardson, Ralph W., Jr., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 990)
    - Roberts, Lewis M., 1975 (Reel 4, Frame 1058)
    - Rohde, Jon E., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 1)
    - Romney, Henry, 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 30)
    - Sadun, Elvio H., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 33)
    - Schoepf, Brooke, 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 36)
    - Scott, Virgil C., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 45)
    - Smeltzer, Dale G., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 165)
    - Spain, James M., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 173)
    - Sprague, Ernest W., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 184)
    - Staff Members Occasional Papers (H-W), 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 188)
    - Starnes, Ordway, 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 344)
    - Stifel, Laurence D., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 382)
    - Stremlau, John J., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 387)
    - Sturrock, Robert F., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 389)
    - Tillman, Allen D., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 392)
    - Todaro, Michael P., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 422)
    - Toenniessen, Gary H., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 429)
    - Turner, Thomas E., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 446)
    - Unrau, Gladwin O., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 448)
    - Upatham, Edward S., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 473)
    - Velazquez Palau, Gabriel, 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 480)
    - Warren, Kenneth S., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 528)
    - Watson, Robert B., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 671)
    - Watt, Earl E., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 676)
    - Waugh, Robert K., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 698)
    - Weaver, Warren, 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 730)
    - Webb, John, 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 732)
    - Webbe, Gerald, 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 735)
    - Weidemann, Wesley C., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 739)
    - Weller, Thomas H., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 747)
    - Wellhausen, Edwin J., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 751)
    - Welsch, Delane E., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 787)
    - Winikoff, Beverly, 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 894)
    - Wortman, L. Sterling, 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 897)
    - Wray, Joe D., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 1133)
    - Wright, Bill C., 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 1159)
    - Young, M. Crawford, 1975 (Reel 5, Frame 1190)
    - Young, William R., 1975 (Reel 6, Frame 1)
  - Requests for Information, 1975; 1975/102
    - C-M, 1975 (Reel 6, Frame 50)
  - International Organizations, 1975; 1975/103
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1975 (Reel 6, Frame 54)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (Supplementary Material), 1975 (Reel 6, Frame 62)
    - International Bank (A-W), 1975 (Reel 6, Frame 234)
    - International Conference on Global Water Law Systems, 1975 (Reel 6, Frame 321)
    - International Environmental Management Seminar, 1975 (Reel 7, Frame 1)
    - International (A-I), 1975 (Reel 7, Frame 389)
    - International (L-W), 1975 (Reel 7, Frame 614)
    - P.E.N. (Congrat-Butlar, Stefan), 1975 (Reel 7, Frame 774)
    - United Nations, Environment Program (January), 1975 (Reel 7, Frame 876)
    - United Nations, Environment Program (February), 1975 (Reel 7, Frame 933)
    - United Nations, Environment Program (March), 1975 (Reel 8, Frame 1)
    - United Nations, Environment Program (April-December), 1975 (Reel 8, Frame 151)
    - United Nations, Environment Program (N-S), 1975 (Reel 8, Frame 425)
    - United Nations, Food and Agriculture Organization (A-W), 1975 (Reel 8, Frame 477)
    - United Nations, Training and Research Institute (J-L), 1975 (Reel 8, Frame 799)
    - United Nations (World Health Organization), 1975 (Reel 8, Frame 899)
    - United Nations, World Health Organization (G-T), 1975 (Reel 9, Frame 1)
    - United Nations (World Population Conference), 1975 (Reel 9, Frame 217)
    - United Nations, World Population Conference (Supplementary Material), 1975 (Reel 9, Frame 245)
    - United Nations (C-M), 1975 (Reel 9, Frame 292)
    - United Nations (R-W), 1975 (Reel 9, Frame 354)
    - United Nations Development Programme (A-T), 1975 (Reel 9, Frame 403)
    - United Nations Educational Scientific and Cultural Organization (A-P), 1975 (Reel 10, Frame 1)
    - United Nations Fund for Population Activities, 1975 (Reel 10, Frame 164)
    - United Nations University, 1975 (Reel 10, Frame 361)
    - A-D, 1975 (Reel 10, Frame 692)
    - G-H, 1975 (Reel 10, Frame 816)
    - I-T, 1975 (Reel 10, Frame 990)
    - World (E-F), 1975 (Reel 11, Frame 1)
    - International Organizations - Declinations Outside Program, 1975; 1975/103.FO
      - United Nations, International Children's Emergency Fund (Film Library), 1975 (Reel 11, Frame 92)
    - International Organizations - Schistosomiasis, 1975; 1975/103.W
      - I-U, 1975 (Reel 11, Frame 103)
  - Agricultural Institute Development, 1975; 1975/104
    - Sellers, Stephen G., 1975 (Reel 11, Frame 139)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 1975; 1975/120
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Roman Empire Conference), 1975 (Reel 11, Frame 147)
    - CIBA Foundation (Paramedic Conference), 1975 (Reel 11, Frame 181)
    - University of Guelph (Bee Conference), 1975 (Reel 11, Frame 290)
    - A-C, 1975 (Reel 11, Frame 312)
    - D, 1975 (Reel 11, Frame 443)
    - E-F, 1975 (Reel 11, Frame 667)
    - G, 1975 (Reel 11, Frame 755)
    - H-I, 1975 (Reel 11, Frame 987)
    - J-K, 1975 (Reel 11, Frame 1102)
    - L-N, 1975 (Reel 12, Frame 1)
    - O-S, 1975 (Reel 12, Frame 82)
    - T-Z, 1975 (Reel 12, Frame 242)
    - Bellagio Study and Conference Center - Declinations, 1975; 1975/120.F
      - Newman, Frank C., 1975 (Reel 12, Frame 365)
  - Rockefeller/Ford Program for Population Policy Research, 1975; 1975/150
    - H-R, 1975 (Reel 12, Frame 383)
  - Conflict in International Relations, 1975; 1975/155
    - Gillespie, John V. (Supplementary Material), 1975 (Reel 12, Frame 493)
    - Johns Hopkins University (Ocean Policy Project), 1975 (Reel 12, Frame 875)
    - Neuman, Stephanie, 1975 (Reel 12, Frame 946)
    - University of Pittsburgh (United States/Cuba Relations), 1975 (Reel 12, Frame 1088)
    - University of Sussex (European Community), 1975 (Reel 12, Frame 1093)
    - A-G, 1975 (Reel 13, Frame 1)
    - H-L, 1975 (Reel 13, Frame 461)
    - N-S, 1975 (Reel 13, Frame 557)
  - United States, 1975; 1975/200
    - Academy of Natural Resources, 1975 (Reel 13, Frame 792)
    - Ab-Af, 1975 (Reel 13, Frame 895)
    - Agricultural Development Council, Inc. (Conference), 1975 (Reel 13, Frame 1060)
    - Agricultural Development Council, Inc. (R-W), 1975 (Reel 14, Frame 1)
    - Alfred University (Hudson, C. B.), 1975 (Reel 14, Frame 239)
    - Ag-Al, 1975 (Reel 14, Frame 241)
    - Alaska Native Foundation (Supplementary Material), 1975 (Reel 14, Frame 352)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Arid Zone Development Conference), 1975 (Reel 14, Frame 601)
    - American Artists Series, 1975 (Reel 14, Frame 790)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science (A-S), 1975 (Reel 14, Frame 870)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, Environmental Programs (Supplementary Material), 1975 (Reel 14, Frame 995)
    - American Council on Education (Overseas Liaison Committee), 1975 (Reel 14, Frame 1066)
    - American Council for Emigres in the Professions, Inc. (Soviet Refugees), 1975 (Reel 14, Frame 1142)
    - American (A-M), 1975 (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - American Universities Field Staff (Bayne), 1975 (Reel 15, Frame 274)
    - American (P-U), 1975 (Reel 15, Frame 277)
    - Amherst College (Ward, John William), 1975 (Reel 15, Frame 448)
    - Anti-Defamation League (Textbook Survey), 1975 (Reel 15, Frame 475)
    - Antioch College (Dixon, James P.), 1975 (Reel 15, Frame 788)
    - Arizona State University, 1975 (Reel 15, Frame 790)
    - Arnett, Roberta, 1975 (Reel 15, Frame 816)
    - Am-Ar, 1975 (Reel 15, Frame 1128)
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies (Law Ethics and Society), 1975 (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges, 1975 (Reel 16, Frame 257)
    - Association of Geoscientists for International Development, 1975 (Reel 16, Frame 304)
    - Association (A-N), 1975 (Reel 16, Frame 368)
    - Atlanta University Center (Library), 1975 (Reel 16, Frame 471)
    - Auburn University (F-W), 1975 (Reel 16, Frame 475)
    - As-Av, 1975 (Reel 16, Frame 491)
    - Baez, Albert V., 1975 (Reel 16, Frame 551)
    - Bastian, Robert K., 1975 (Reel 16, Frame 654)
    - Ba, 1975 (Reel 16, Frame 722)
    - Bennett College, New York (Dance), 1975 (Reel 16, Frame 867)
    - Bennington College (Arts), 1975 (Reel 16, Frame 953)
    - Be-Bi, 1975 (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - Bl, 1975 (Reel 17, Frame 382)
    - Boston State College (Unified Studies Program), 1975 (Reel 17, Frame 431)
    - Boston State College, Unified Studies Program (Supplementary Material), 1975 (Reel 17, Frame 606)
    - Boston University (A-J), 1975 (Reel 17, Frame 683)
    - Bo, 1975 (Reel 17, Frame 696)
    - Briarcliff College (Bunting, Josiah), 1975 (Reel 17, Frame 744)
    - Brookings Institution (A-B), 1975 (Reel 17, Frame 747)
    - Brookings Institution (Salant, Walter S.), 1975 (Reel 17, Frame 858)
    - Brookings Institution, Salant, Walter S. (Supplementary Material), 1975 (Reel 17, Frame 862)
    - Brown University (F-V), 1975 (Reel 17, Frame 1124)
    - Br, 1975 (Reel 17, Frame 1166)
    - Bueding, Ernest, 1975 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - Bu-By, 1975 (Reel 18, Frame 3)
    - California Institute of Technology (Environment), 1975 (Reel 18, Frame 167)
    - California Institute of Technology (Supplementary Material), 1975 (Reel 18, Frame 181)
    - Carnegie Endowment (I-U), 1975 (Reel 18, Frame 278)
    - Case Western Reserve University (B-C), 1975 (Reel 18, Frame 358)
    - Catholic Relief Services (Rural Development), 1975 (Reel 18, Frame 367)
    - Catholic University, Washington (Chavez, Rebeca P.), 1975 (Reel 18, Frame 446)
    - Ca, 1975 (Reel 18, Frame 468)
    - Center for Biology of Natural Systems (Kohl, Daniel H.), 1975 (Reel 18, Frame 705)
    - Center for Community Change, 1975 (Reel 18, Frame 746)
    - Center for Policy Research, Inc. (Social Sciences and Humanities), 1975 (Reel 18, Frame 900)
    - Center for the Study of Noise in Society, 1975 (Reel 18, Frame 963)
    - Center (A-U), 1975 (Reel 18, Frame 1002)
    - Center for a Voluntary Society, 1975 (Reel 19, Frame 1)
    - Center for War/Peace Studies, 1975 (Reel 19, Frame 97)
    - Ce, 1975 (Reel 19, Frame 219)
    - China Consultants International, Ltd., 1975 (Reel 19, Frame 240)
    - Ch, 1975 (Reel 19, Frame 259)
    - City College of New York (E-U), 1975 (Reel 19, Frame 456)
    - City University of New York (A-W), 1975 (Reel 19, Frame 494)
    - Ci, 1975 (Reel 19, Frame 703)
    - Claremont (C-M), 1975 (Reel 19, Frame 742)
    - Clarkson College of Technology (P-W), 1975 (Reel 19, Frame 772)
    - Cleveland State University (Bodenhorn, Diran), 1975 (Reel 19, Frame 792)
    - Cl, 1975 (Reel 19, Frame 795)
    - Colgate University (Composer Visits), 1975 (Reel 19, Frame 909)
    - College of Design (Art Center), 1975 (Reel 19, Frame 920)
    - Colorado State University (A-W), 1975 (Reel 19, Frame 924)
    - Columbia University (I-W), 1975 (Reel 20, Frame 1)
    - Coa-Col, 1975 (Reel 20, Frame 345)
    - Committee on Scholarly Communication with the People's Republic of China, 1975 (Reel 20, Frame 700)